Here's a quick
overview. We
define a
depth-first
search function
that takes a graph
and a starting
vertex as input.
define a
depth-first
search function
that takes a graph
and a starting
vertex as input.
Then we
initialize a set
to keep track of
visited vertices
and a stack with
the starting
vertex. Next, we
Then we
initialize a set
to keep track of
visited vertices
and a stack with
the starting
vertex. Next, we
iterate through
the stack.
vertex. Next, we
iterate through
the stack.
popping vertices
and marking them
as visited if they
haven't been
visited before.
popping vertices
and marking them
as visited if they
haven't been
visited before.
So finally, we
explore the graph
by
adding unvisited
neighbors to the
stack.
So finally, we
explore the graph
by
adding unvisited
neighbors to the
stack.